novatek.com.tw 2010-06-25

# Welcome to Novatek

This Privacy Policy states the information collection and use policy of this website ([www.novatek.com.tw](http://www.novatek.com.tw/)), including under what circumstances the information may be collected, what type of information may be collected, how the information is used and with whom the information may be shared. This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to the information which is collected through this website.

This Privacy Policy forms a part of the Terms of Use of this website. Please read the Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy carefully before you use this website. By accessing, browsing and/or using this website or uploading/downloading any Materials to or from this website, you acknowledge your acceptance of the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to either the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website

The collection and use of personal information  
If a visitor of this website wishes to receive Novatek’s newsletters and information, to participate in Novatek’s activities and events, or to apply for jobs at Novatek etc, the visitor may need to submit his/her requests and/or his/her personal resume to us via this website which request or resume may contain his/her personal information, such as name, title, company, address, e-mail address, phone numbers, personal ID numbers, and date of birth. **Novatek may use and you hereby agree Novatek may use this personal information to respond to your requests, your job application, and/or to contact you via the personal information provided by you to send you Novatek’s e-newsletter or inform you of any new products, services or promotions we, our subsidiaries or affiliated company may offer. If you do not wish to receive such information, simply tell us to remove your name from our mailing list by sending us an e-mail.**

The collection and use of non-personal information  
Please note that we may provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related website information to third parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

The protection/sharing/publication of your personal information  
Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing personal information, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet, and no system of technology is completely safe or “hacker- proof", Novatek will endeavor to take appropriate steps to ensure that your personally information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.

Unless otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy or agreed by you, we will not disclose, sell or provide your personal information to unaffiliated third parties. By submitting your information, you hereby agree that:

  1.  **The information you provide will be used and shared with Novatek and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies.**
  2. Novatek may possibly disclose your personal information in special cases when we have reasons to do so for any or all of the following: (1) requirements by laws and regulations; (2) to comply with legal process or governmental requests; (3) to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating this website's Terms of Use or may be violating Novatek's or others' rights or causing injury to or interference with Novatek's or others' property and/or interest; and/or (4) to protect the rights, property, or safety of Novatek, the visitors/users of the website, or the public. 

The use of cookies  
We do not use cookies on this website to collect information on or from our visitors/users; except that the "e-service" function of this website contains cookie(s) to read visitors/user names, passwords, recorders or other information.

Changes  
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the revised Privacy Policy posting on our website. Any use of this website after such posting shall be deemed to constitute acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy by you.

Additional Information  
Questions regarding this policy should be directed to [webmaster@novatek.com.tw](mailto:webmaster@novatek.com.tw) . You may also contact us at:

Novatek Microelectronics Corp.  
2F, No. 13, Innovation Rd I, Hsinchu Science Park, Hsinchu 300, Taiwan, R.O.C.  
TEL：886-3-567-0889  
FAX：886-3-577-0132
